<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>books on علیرضا یونسی</title>
    <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/tags/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in books on علیرضا یونسی</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fa</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:30:03 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/tags/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Sex and Repression in Savage Society,” by Bronisław Malinowski</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/sex-and-repression-in-savage-society-by-bronis%C5%82aw-malinowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/sex-and-repression-in-savage-society-by-bronis%C5%82aw-malinowski/</guid>
      <description>In his seminal work, “Sex and Repression in Savage Society,” Bronisław Malinowski delves deep into the intricate nuances of human sexuality within indigenous cultures, unearthing a treasure trove of enlightening observations and thought-provoking analyses. Employing his astute anthropological lens, Malinowski transports readers into captivating narratives of tribal societies, skillfully interweaving empirical evidence with lyrical descriptions of exotic rituals and customs.
Malinowski’s scholarly prowess is artfully showcased in his meticulous examination of the multifaceted dynamics governing sexual practices in these savage societies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Hobbes and Political Obedience: Insights from the English Civil War</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>Thomas Hobbes, a philosopher hailing from 17th-century England, offers valuable insights into the intricate matter of political obedience. His analysis delves into the extent to which we should patiently submit to rulers, particularly those who are lacking in adequacy, and when it becomes justifiable to initiate revolutions and overthrow governments in the pursuit of an improved society. Hobbes’s perspective is tightly intertwined with a significant event that deeply influenced his beliefs: the English civil war, which took place when he was 64 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dante</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/dante/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/dante/</guid>
      <description>The New Life Much of the life of Dante Alighieri is obscure, and the known facts are surrounded by a haze of legend and conjecture. He was born in Florence in 1265, of a family noble but not wealthy. His early education is a matter of inference, but we know that he learned the art of writing verse from the poets of France and Provence, and that after he reached manhood he devoted much time to study and became profoundly learned.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
