<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>politics on علیرضا یونسی</title>
    <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/tags/politics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in politics on علیرضا یونسی</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fa</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:34:17 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/tags/politics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:34:17 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/about/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! I&amp;rsquo;m Alireza Yoonesi, a law student with a passion for the intricate dance of the legal world and the limitless possibilities of technology. I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to welcome you to my corner of the digital realm where the realms of law and code intersect.
A Multifaceted Journey My journey has been nothing short of diverse. While my days at Duke Law School nurtured my fascination for the intricacies of Private Law, my insatiable curiosity led me down a myriad of paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Hobbes and Political Obedience: Insights from the English Civil War</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>Thomas Hobbes, a philosopher hailing from 17th-century England, offers valuable insights into the intricate matter of political obedience. His analysis delves into the extent to which we should patiently submit to rulers, particularly those who are lacking in adequacy, and when it becomes justifiable to initiate revolutions and overthrow governments in the pursuit of an improved society. Hobbes’s perspective is tightly intertwined with a significant event that deeply influenced his beliefs: the English civil war, which took place when he was 64 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Munger on Constitutions</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/michael-munger-on-constitutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/michael-munger-on-constitutions/</guid>
      <description>Intro I first got to know Dr. Munger on YouTube(Why Major in Political Science?) when I wanted to decide between going to Law school &amp;amp; studying Political Science back in 2021. Though I was persuaded by the guy to do so and he influenced me for the rest of my life with his Germany stories, and his BMW car, I decided to go to Law school for better job status. Anyways, his ideas on constitutions have always been fascinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Kamikaze Drone — Shahed 136</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/iranian-kamikaze-drone-shahed-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/iranian-kamikaze-drone-shahed-136/</guid>
      <description>While the Kalibr 3M14, a Russian competitor to the American-made Tomahawk missile, costs the Russian military one million dollars (or roughly six million dollars for export), the Iranian Kamikaze drone has a price tag of fewer than twenty-five thousand dollars, which is half the average price of a car in the US and roughly one percent of the Tomahawk price tag. It appears to be a low-cost cruise missile that can be effective when fired in groups.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
