<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>علیرضا یونسی</title>
    <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/</link>
    <description>Recent content on علیرضا یونسی</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fa</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:38:15 +0330</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>سلام دنیا</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/salam-donya/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 05:38:15 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/salam-donya/</guid>
      <description>به گفته تمام فلاسفه، سخت‌ترین پرسشی که می‌توان مطرح کرد، این سوال است که: «فلسفه چیست؟»
در حقیقت، هیچ‌گاه نمی‌توان گفت فلسفه چیست؛ یعنی هیچ‌گاه نمی‌توان گفت: فلسفه این است و جز این نیست؛ زیرا فلسفه، آزادترین نوع فعالیت آدمی است و نمی‌توان آن را محدود به امری خاص کرد.
عمر فلسفه به اندازه عمر انسان بر روی زمین است و در طول تاریخ تغییرات فراوانی کرده و هر زمان به گونه‌ای متفاوت با دیگر دوره‌ها بوده است.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 03:08:28 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/contact/</guid>
      <description>Let&amp;rsquo;s Connect: Feel free to reach out with questions, collaboration ideas, or simply to say hello. I&amp;rsquo;m just a message away!
Your Thoughts Matter: Your feedback and inquiries are invaluable. Drop me a line, and let&amp;rsquo;s start a meaningful conversation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 02:34:17 +0330</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/about/</guid>
      <description>Greetings! I&amp;rsquo;m Alireza Yoonesi, a law student with a passion for the intricate dance of the legal world and the limitless possibilities of technology. I&amp;rsquo;m delighted to welcome you to my corner of the digital realm where the realms of law and code intersect.
A Multifaceted Journey My journey has been nothing short of diverse. While my days at Duke Law School nurtured my fascination for the intricacies of Private Law, my insatiable curiosity led me down a myriad of paths.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World!</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/hello-world/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>“Sex and Repression in Savage Society,” by Bronisław Malinowski</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/sex-and-repression-in-savage-society-by-bronis%C5%82aw-malinowski/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/sex-and-repression-in-savage-society-by-bronis%C5%82aw-malinowski/</guid>
      <description>In his seminal work, “Sex and Repression in Savage Society,” Bronisław Malinowski delves deep into the intricate nuances of human sexuality within indigenous cultures, unearthing a treasure trove of enlightening observations and thought-provoking analyses. Employing his astute anthropological lens, Malinowski transports readers into captivating narratives of tribal societies, skillfully interweaving empirical evidence with lyrical descriptions of exotic rituals and customs.
Malinowski’s scholarly prowess is artfully showcased in his meticulous examination of the multifaceted dynamics governing sexual practices in these savage societies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thomas Hobbes and Political Obedience: Insights from the English Civil War</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 15:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/thomas-hobbes-and-political-obedience-insights-from-the-english-civil-war/</guid>
      <description>Thomas Hobbes, a philosopher hailing from 17th-century England, offers valuable insights into the intricate matter of political obedience. His analysis delves into the extent to which we should patiently submit to rulers, particularly those who are lacking in adequacy, and when it becomes justifiable to initiate revolutions and overthrow governments in the pursuit of an improved society. Hobbes’s perspective is tightly intertwined with a significant event that deeply influenced his beliefs: the English civil war, which took place when he was 64 years old.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Munger on Constitutions</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/michael-munger-on-constitutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/michael-munger-on-constitutions/</guid>
      <description>Intro I first got to know Dr. Munger on YouTube(Why Major in Political Science?) when I wanted to decide between going to Law school &amp;amp; studying Political Science back in 2021. Though I was persuaded by the guy to do so and he influenced me for the rest of my life with his Germany stories, and his BMW car, I decided to go to Law school for better job status. Anyways, his ideas on constitutions have always been fascinating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iranian Kamikaze Drone — Shahed 136</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/iranian-kamikaze-drone-shahed-136/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/iranian-kamikaze-drone-shahed-136/</guid>
      <description>While the Kalibr 3M14, a Russian competitor to the American-made Tomahawk missile, costs the Russian military one million dollars (or roughly six million dollars for export), the Iranian Kamikaze drone has a price tag of fewer than twenty-five thousand dollars, which is half the average price of a car in the US and roughly one percent of the Tomahawk price tag. It appears to be a low-cost cruise missile that can be effective when fired in groups.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Was Shakespeare Thinking Back Then?</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/what-was-shakespeare-thinking-back-then/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/what-was-shakespeare-thinking-back-then/</guid>
      <description>Manifesto These days, I got nothing to do but Hydrate and do some codes on personal projects, read books and articles, and of course, Hydrate again, just like in the Jarhead (2005).
A few days ago, I was wondering about what Shakespeare was thinking (and writing), and at the same time, I was working on a project that revealed what YouTube creators were thinking based on Word-Clouds from their videos. It takes the URL of a video and returns the Word-Cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dante</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/dante/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 11:30:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/posts/dante/</guid>
      <description>The New Life Much of the life of Dante Alighieri is obscure, and the known facts are surrounded by a haze of legend and conjecture. He was born in Florence in 1265, of a family noble but not wealthy. His early education is a matter of inference, but we know that he learned the art of writing verse from the poets of France and Provence, and that after he reached manhood he devoted much time to study and became profoundly learned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Archive</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/archives/</guid>
      <description>archives</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://fa.AYoonesi.ir/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
